NAUFAL FADHIL ATHALLAH

Bogor, Jawa Barat, 16913

linkedin.com/in/naufalfadhil | hello.naufalfadhil@gmail.com | github.com/naufalfadhil

SUMMARY

I love **collaboration**, **challenge**, **competition**, **learn** technologies and **create** a new things to **problem solve** use technologies. **Professionally**, I have worked as developer. **Personally** I have a quick understand to learn new knowledge, can work in under pressure, and helpful such directed my friends in college programming assignments.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS GUNADARMA

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING (2019 - 2023)

- Grade Point Average (GPA 5.58)
- Assistant Laboratorium, Specialist at Developer

SMK BANGUN NUSA BANGSA

COMPUTER AND NETWORK ENGINEERING (2016 - 2019)

- Top 4 Highest UN Scores
- Take a robotics extracurricular
- Network implementation for national exam

WORK EXPERIENCE

ASOSIASI ASURANSI JIWA INDONESIA

WEB PROGRAMMER (MAY 2021 - PRESENT)

As web programmer, my responsibility and achivements included:

- Maintained web Asosiasi Asuransi Jiwa Indonesia
- Managed database Asosiasi Asuransi Jiwa Indonesia
- Help staff with daily technical problems

GUNADARMA UNIVERSITY COMPUTING CENTER

DEVELOPER (NOV 2020 – PRESENT)

As developer, my responsibility and achivements included:

- Maintained web Universitas Gunadarma
- Programmed metadata JSON Sistem Kelembagaan DIKTI

CV AEROSMART TECHNOLOGY INDONESIA

STUDENT INTERN (MARCH 2018 - MAY 2018)

As student intern, my responsibility and achivements included:

- Reach 1000 data entries equals to staff target
- Sort formulir paper document
- Data entry for regional government and election data supporter

SKILL AND KNOWLEDGE

Android : Java, Kotlin

• Basic : **Python**, C++, Ruby

• Web : **HTML**, **CSS**, **PHP**, JS, **Laravel**, Codeigniter

Database : Oracle, PHPMyAdmin, Microsoft SQL Server, Postgres

ACHIEVEMENT & PROJECT

IDCAMP 2020 DEVELOPER CHALLENGE: MENGUBAH DUNIA MELALUI INOVASI TEKNOLOGISelected as one of **50 Winners** from **70+ Participants** and **552 Challenge Followers** for create fake university named Google University for education technology, design, and bussiness on google scope. This website to solve the problem Quality Education at SDG Sustainble Development Goals 2030.

BOGOR INDEPENDENCE DAY 2017

2nd Place of Winner from 6+ Team in Robotics Category for add new features on Smart Park Prototype:

- Use LDR Sensor to make automatical turn on and off the lamp park
- Use humidity sensor to check the humidty of dirt so if dirt dry, alarm will be sound and plant not dry again.
- Make a smart trash. If People will throw the garbage. The cover will be open automatically.

BOGOR YOUNG SCIENTIST FAIR 2017

3rd **Place** of Winner from **5+ Team** in Robotics Category of **31 Team** Participants for created Smart Park Prototype from problem in the park "how to people for not steped on grass?". So my friend and I make a problem solve with robotical concept. We're use proximity sensor, If someone through the electomagnetic sensor. The sensor will send to speaker, its will be sounding and give information to the park guard.

CERTIFICATE

- Belajar Fundamental Front-end Web Development Dicoding
- Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula Dicoding
- Belajar Machine Learning untuk Pemula Dicoding

LANGUAGE

Indonesian : NativeEnglish : Intermediate

OTHER

Website : https://naufalfadhil.github.io
Medium : https://naufal-fadhil.medium.com
Behance : https://www.behance.net/naufal-fadhil
Certificates : https://naufalfadhil.github.io/certificates